All you need is one killer track.
Baby Driver is a action, crime film directed by Edgar Wright.
After being coerced into working for a crime boss, a young getaway
driver finds himself taking part in a heist doomed to fail.
Baby, played by Ansel Elgort.
Doc, played by Kevin Spacey.
Debora, played by Lily James.
Buddy, played by Jon Hamm.
Bats, played by Jamie Foxx.
Griff, played by Jon Bernthal.
Baby Driver is a 2017 action thriller film written and directed by Edgar Wright.
It stars Ansel Elgort as Baby, a getaway driver seeking freedom from a
life of crime with his girlfriend Debora (Lily James).
Kevin Spacey, Jon Hamm, Eiza González, Jon Bernthal and
Jamie Foxx appear in supporting roles.
Eric Fellner and his Working Title Films partner Tim Bevan produced Baby
Driver in association with Big Talk Productions' Nira Park.
Sony and TriStar Pictures handled commercial distribution of the film.
Baby Driver was financed through tax subsidies from the Georgia state
government and a co-production pact between TriStar and MRC.
Wright developed Baby Driver for over two decades.
He devised the idea in his youth, and his early directing
experience further shaped his ambitions for Baby Driver.
Originally based in Los Angeles, Wright chose Atlanta as the film's setting after the studio secured tax credits
to subsidize production costs, integrating the city's ethos into an important storytelling device.
Principal photography took place in Atlanta from February to May 2016.
Production involved the planning of meticulously coordinated
stunts, choreography, and
in-camera effects.
Thematic studies of Baby Driver examine patterns of color
symbolism and Baby's evolving morality.
Baby Driver premiered at the South by Southwest festival on March 11, 2017,
followed by releases in North America and the United Kingdom on June 28.
The media praised the film's craftsmanship and actors, though
certain aspects of the writing were sources of criticism.
The National Board of Review selected Baby Driver as
one of the top films of the year.
It earned $227 million globally, bolstered by positive word-of-mouth
support and flagging interest in blockbuster franchises.
Baby Driver was nominated for numerous awards, including three Academy Awards, two BAFTA Film Awards (with a win for Editing), two Critics' Choice Awards (again, with a win
for Editing), and a Golden Globe for Best Actor - Musical or Comedy nomination for Elgort, and won several other honors, chiefly for technical achievement.
The success of Baby Driver increased studio interest in producing a sequel.
The film explores themes of robbery, waitress, atlanta, crime boss, romance.